(Penny:)You'll never believe
what happened to me at work.
(Penny:)This old guy was choking on his food
and I saved his life.
(Leonard:)Did you Heimlich him?
(Penny:)No, I said,
"I think that old guy's choking."
Then one of the busboys Heimlich'd him.
(Leonard:)You're a hero.
(Penny:)Yeah, that was the point of the story.
(Leonard:)Do you know
if you have Thursday night off?
Uh, I think so, why?
(Leonard:)Why? It's Valentine's Day.
(Penny:)Oh, right.
Yeah, we can do something.
- You could be a little more into it.
- I'm into it, I'm into it.
There's pressure to make the night special
and it never works out.
Well, this time it's gonna be different
because I'm like a romance ninja. Heh.
You don't see it coming and then... Bam!
Romance! Watch out! Hearts, kisses, love!
Ooh! Ya!
(Penny:)Sometimes I think I've made you
cooler than you used to be...
(Penny:)...then you go
and do that.
(Sheldon:)So in conclusion,
I believe the painful sensation felt...
(Sheldon:)...after passing a meal
of spicy chilies is proof...
(Sheldon:)...that the rectum does possess
the sense of taste.
(Amy:)I concur, but you changed the subject.
What are we doing for Valentine's Day?
(Sheldon:)Oh, you caught that, did you?